<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Welcome</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ww.docs.stord.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ww.docs.stord.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 19:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>There was a plot to assassinate Queen Elizabeth II in the United States</title>
		<link>https://ww.docs.stord.com/there-was-a-plot-to-assassinate-queen-elizabeth-ii-in-the-united-states/</link>
					<comments>https://ww.docs.stord.com/there-was-a-plot-to-assassinate-queen-elizabeth-ii-in-the-united-states/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 19:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Queen Elizabeth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ww.docs.stord.com/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Queen Elizabeth II visited the United States in 1983. There were threats that he might [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Queen Elizabeth II visited the United States in 1983. There were threats that he might be assassinated. This is known from the recently released documents of the United States Central Bureau of Investigation (FBI).</p>



<p>Under the Right to Information Act, US media organizations requested information about Queen Elizabeth II&#8217;s visit to the United States. Following their request, 102 pages of documents about Rani were released on the FBI&#8217;s website &#8216;Vault&#8217; last Monday.</p>



<p>The Irish Republican Army (IRA) threatened to kill the Queen, according to a document. The FBI, which was in charge of the Queen&#8217;s security on that trip, was very concerned about this. The threat to kill Queen was made by a San Francisco police officer. He then reported the matter to FBI agents.</p>



<p>The police officer, who frequented an Irish pub, told FBI agents that a man he had seen at the Irish pub had called him and said he wanted revenge for his daughter&#8217;s murder. He claimed that his daughter was killed by rubber bullets in Northern Ireland.</p>



<p>The death threat was made on February 4, 1983, about a month before Queen Elizabeth II and her husband Prince Philip visited California.</p>



<p>According to the document, the person who threatened to kill wanted to harm the queen by any means. He said he would try to assassinate the Queen when her royal yacht Britannia passes under the Golden Gate Bridge, drop a heavy object from the bridge, or when she visits Yosemite National Park.</p>



<p>Upon learning of this threat, the Secret Service planned to &#8216;close the walkways over the Golden Gate Bridge as the yacht approached&#8217;. However, the document does not clearly mention what action was taken in Yosemite National Park. But the Queen visited the park.</p>



<p>The FBI has not released any details on whether anyone was arrested in the incident.</p>



<p>During Queen Elizabeth II&#8217;s several state visits to the United States, including this one in 1983, tensions in Northern Ireland were known as the &#8216;Troubles in Northern Ireland&#8217;.</p>



<p>Queen Elizabeth II previously visited New York City in 1976 to attend the 200th anniversary of the United States&#8217; independence.</p>



<p>Documents reveal how a pilot was instructed to fly a small plane over Battery Park with the words &#8216;Exit England, Ireland&#8217;.</p>



<p>According to the documents, the FBI was then on high alert for Rani&#8217;s assassination threats. Lord Mountbatten, a relative of the Queen, was killed in a bomb attack off the coast of County Sligo in the Republic of Ireland in 1979. The bombing was carried out by the Irish Republican Army.</p>



<p>In 1989, the FBI released internal documents, or memos, about Queen&#8217;s personal visit to Kentucky. It read, &#8216;The Irish Republican Army is still a threat to the British monarchy&#8217;.</p>



<p>The document also said, &#8216;Boston and New York authorities have been asked to be on alert for any IRA threats against the Queen. Louisville, Kentucky will also be called immediately.&#8217;</p>



<p>The late Queen Elizabeth II had a keen interest in horse racing. The Queen had her own racehorse. He visited Kentucky several times during his lifetime to enjoy horse racing.</p>



<p>In 1991, the Queen was scheduled to watch a Baltimore Orioles baseball game with then-US President George H. Bush on a state visit.</p>



<p>The FBI warned the Secret Service that &#8216;Irish groups&#8217; were planning demonstrations at the stadium. For this &#8216;an Irish group bought the bulk of the grandstand tickets&#8217;.</p>



<p>The FBI told NBC News there may be &#8220;additional documents&#8221; beyond those released this week. However, the date of when they can be published has not been fixed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ww.docs.stord.com/there-was-a-plot-to-assassinate-queen-elizabeth-ii-in-the-united-states/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Controversy over placing gold bars in India&#8217;s new parliament building</title>
		<link>https://ww.docs.stord.com/controversy-over-placing-gold-bars-in-indias-new-parliament-building/</link>
					<comments>https://ww.docs.stord.com/controversy-over-placing-gold-bars-in-indias-new-parliament-building/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 19:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Narendra Modi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Parliament building]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the building]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ww.docs.stord.com/?p=8</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Controversy is not leaving behind India&#8217;s new parliament building. After all the controversies and criticisms, [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Controversy is not leaving behind India&#8217;s new parliament building. After all the controversies and criticisms, the opening phase is starting on Sunday morning. Prime Minister Narendra Modi will inaugurate. A new controversy has also arisen over keeping &#8216;Sengal&#8217;, a gold bar studded with ancient jewels, in the new building.</p>



<p>Prime Minister launched the Rs 24,000-crore &#8216;Central Vista&#8217; project amidst India&#8217;s ailing economy amid the Covid situation. The new parliament building is a part of that project. At that time, the necessity of this project was discussed in various quarters. There was also a public interest litigation.</p>



<p>However, the new parliament building was built by overcoming all obstacles and ignoring all objections. Its opening phase is going to start from 7:30 am on Sunday. It will end at two o&#8217;clock.</p>



<p>At the center of the debate in the early stages was the necessity of the decision. It takes a new form when it comes to the opening phase. The president of the country is the guardian of the parliament. The session of Parliament started and ended at his call. The budget session of Parliament starts every year with the President&#8217;s address to the joint session of the members of the two chambers. Why is the head of government inaugurating a new building leaving that guardian behind, the country is in turmoil.</p>



<p>Despite the majority of opposition parties deciding to boycott the event, the government remained firm. According to the calendar, Prime Minister Narendra Modi will arrive at the new building at 7:30 am to start the program on the 14th day of Jaishtha Ashtami Tithi. At 7:30 p.m., worship-archana and yajna ceremony started.</p>



<p>The debate about why Hinduism is the seat of democracy in secular India, which arose during the foundation stone laying ceremony of the new Parliament building, may also arise this time. But the question of the service was unsettled by the government, it will surely be unsettled this time too.</p>



<p>Controversy has arisen over &#8216;Sengal&#8217;, an ancient gem-studded gold bar. It was the custom of the Chola dynasty that ruled the Deccan in ancient times to hand over Sengal to the new king. The exchange of tiles was symbolic of the transfer of power. Union Home Minister Amit Shah claims that Lord Mountbatten, the last viceroy of British India, handed over the golden rod to Sengal Jawaharlal Nehru on the eve of independence. That was done on the advice of the last Governor General Chakraborty Rajagopalachari. Accordingly, a brick is made. Mountbatten gave that brick to Nehru. Nehru kept the brick in a collection in Allahabad.</p>



<p>From there, the Modi government recovered it and brought it to Delhi. On Sunday, Sengal will have his place in the Lok Sabha of the new Parliament building. By giving this information, Amit Shah taunted the Congress and said that this is the proof of how indifferent the Congress is to the ancient traditions of the country.</p>



<p>This demand of the government has also been debated. Congress has officially said that Sengal&#8217;s story is completely fabricated. There is no record anywhere that Mountbatten transferred power through a single transfer. On that night of August 14, there was no such official event. It is not even mentioned in any official description. There is no picture anywhere of Mountbatten handing Nehru the single. The whole claim is fictitious.</p>



<p>According to historians, a monk from a monastery in Tamil Nadu visited Nehru&#8217;s residence and handed it over to him. Nehru accepted it. That information is there. That brick was kept in the Allahabad Museum.</p>



<p>Chakraborty Rajagopalachari&#8217;s grandson and biographer Rajmohan Gandhi wrote in an article about the controversy that he was unaware of the exchange of tiles as part of the transfer of power ceremony. The government should make public all official documents on the matter when the government demands it.</p>



<p>This controversy has also become big around the inauguration of the new parliament building. At the same time, politics is also raising its head. The opposition alleges that the BJP is trying to use Sengal to gain control of the land under its feet in Tamil Nadu.</p>



<p>The Prime Minister will come to the Lok Sabha at 8:30 am after the puja on Sunday. There the gold bar will be placed near the Speaker&#8217;s seat. Then there will be a prayer meeting in the lobby. Modi will return after the prayer meeting at 9:30 am. Will come again at 12 noon. Another event will begin with the national anthem. Deputy Chairman of the Rajya Sabha Harivansh will read the speech and message of the Guardian President Draupadi Murmu and Vice President Jagdeep Dhankhar. Mallikarjun Kharg, Leader of Opposition in the Rajya Sabha Congress, was scheduled to deliver the address. But the Congress is boycotting the event. Lok Sabha Speaker Om Birla will deliver the address. The Prime Minister will release a commemorative coin of Rs 75 on the occasion of 75 years of Independence. The program will end at 2 pm with Modi&#8217;s speech.</p>



<p>Controversy will still remain in GEE. The new parliament building has 888 seats in the Lok Sabha and 350 in the Rajya Sabha. At present there are 543 members in the Lok Sabha and 250 in the Rajya Sabha. The increase in population will also increase the number of representatives from state to state in the future. The debate has already started.</p>



<p>Because birth control is successful in all states of South India. The number of representatives of North India will be much higher than those of those states. Because population control in the Hindi belt is not as successful as in the south. As a result, the dominant party in the North would rule the country without the support of the Deccan. Politicians of Deccan have become involved in this.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ww.docs.stord.com/controversy-over-placing-gold-bars-in-indias-new-parliament-building/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simeone&#8217;s son in the Argentina team, except Dybala-Martinez</title>
		<link>https://ww.docs.stord.com/simeones-son-in-the-argentina-team-except-dybala-martinez/</link>
					<comments>https://ww.docs.stord.com/simeones-son-in-the-argentina-team-except-dybala-martinez/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina team]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ww.docs.stord.com/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lionel Messi&#8217;s first two matches in Argentina&#8217;s three-star jersey must not have been forgotten! Not [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Lionel Messi&#8217;s first two matches in Argentina&#8217;s three-star jersey must not have been forgotten! Not to forget. As the people of Argentina saluted their World Cup winning team, Messi was the one; Hard to forget for any Argentina fan either.</p>



<p>After winning the World Cup in Qatar in December last year, Argentina played two friendlies against Panama and Curacao in March this year, which became the stage for the festival. In June, Argentina will play again in a friendly match. Albiceleste will play two matches in Asia tour. Australia will face Messi&#8217;s opponents in Beijing, China on June 15, and the host Indonesia will face them in Jakarta on June 19.</p>



<p>Argentine coach Lionel Scaloni has announced the 27-member squad for these two matches today. Giovanni Simeone got the call after 5 years. The 27-year-old striker is the son of Atletico Madrid coach Diego Simeone. After 33 years, Napoli won the Italian Serie &#8216;A&#8217;. Simeone contributed a lot to the Naples team to win the league title. His great performance did not go unnoticed by Scaloni.</p>



<p>In addition, Leonardo Balerdi, the defender of Olympique Marseille, returned to the team after 4 years. And the new face is Dutch club PSV Eindhoven goalkeeper Waltar Benitez.</p>



<p>However, the two World Cup winning forwards Paulo Dybala and Lautaro Martinez were not kept in the team. Dybala recently suffered an ankle injury. Martinez also has an ankle injury. However, he will undergo treatment after playing the Champions League final for Inter Milan. They have not been considered for the national team until they fully recover before the next club season.</p>



<p>Argentina team for Asia tour</p>



<p>Goalkeepers: Emiliano Martinez, Geranimo Rulli, Walter Benitez.</p>



<p>Defence: Nahuel Molina, Gonzalo Montiel, German Pezza, Cristian Romero, Leonardo Balerdi, Nicolas Otamendi, Facundo Medina, Nicolas Taliafico, Marcos Acuña.</p>



<p>Midfield: Leonardo Paredes, Enzo Fernandez, Guido Rodriguez, Rodrigo Di Paul, Ezekiel Palacios, Alexis McAllister, Thiago Almada, Giovanni Lo Celso.</p>



<p>Attack: Lucas Ocampos, Angel Di Maria, Julian Alvarez, Giovanni Simeone, Alejandro Garnacho, Nicolas Gonzalez, Lionel Messi.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ww.docs.stord.com/simeones-son-in-the-argentina-team-except-dybala-martinez/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://ww.docs.stord.com/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://ww.docs.stord.com/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://ww.docs.stord.com/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ww.docs.stord.com/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
